{
    "question": "Quiz ;)    Aldo left his favourite restaurant at 11 o\u2019clock. It was warm evening and decided to walk along the beach. Suddenly, four masked girls aged about seventeen came up to \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 and asked for the street.\r\n\r\nA. Him\r\nB. Her\r\nC. You\r\nD. Me\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p>\u27a1\ufe0f A Him </p><p></p><h3>Question</h3><p>Aldo left his favourite restaurant at 11 o\u2019clock. It was warm evening and decided to walk along the beach. Suddenly, four masked girls aged about seventeen came up to \u2026\u2026and asked for the street.</p><p>A. Him</p><p>B. Her</p><p>C. You</p><p>D. Me</p><p></p><h3>Translat </h3><p>Aldo meninggalkan restoran favoritnya pada pukul 11.  Itu adalah malam yang hangat dan memutuskan untuk berjalan di sepanjang pantai.  Tiba-tiba, empat gadis bertopeng berusia sekitar tujuh belas datang ke \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 dan meminta jalan.</p><p></p><p> A. Dia</p><p> B. Dia</p><p> C. Anda</p><p> D. Saya</p><p></p><h3>Answer</h3><p>A. Him</p><p></p><h3>Explanation</h3><p>Explain as a pronoun he is male is him, he, .</p><p>while the pronoun in female her, she,</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "which-one-ischemistry-or-phisics-155",
            "question": "Which one is...chemistry or phisics?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Yang mana... kimia atau fisika</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "do-you-think-its-important-to-educate-people-about-endanger-spec-462",
            "question": "Do you think it's important to educate people about endanger species?    a.\r\n\r\nNot, it isn't.\r\n\r\nb.\r\n\r\nNo important.\r\n\r\nc.\r\n\r\nYes, it is.\r\n\r\nd.\r\n\r\nYes, there are not.\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>The answer is C. Yes, it is</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>yes,it is</p><p>ratinya ya itu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-write-ab-or-c-tulislah-ab-atau-c-1-my-hobby-is-me-259",
            "question": "B. Write a,b, or c ( Tulislah a,b atau c)!    1. My hobby is ... (Memasak)\r\n2. Two mother is meaning ...\r\n3. Teacher How are you?\r\nStudent\r\nThank you\r\n4. Anggur is\r\n5. Cat eats\r\n6. I like playing football\r\nFootball is\r\n7. Empat pisang kuning is.\r\n8. Indonesian flag is ..... And\r\n9. Teacher Riri is my English\r\n(Guru)\r\n10. Father is\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> 1. Cooking</p><p></p><p>2. Step mother / second mother</p><p></p><p>3. I&#039;m fine, thank you</p><p></p><p>4. Grape</p><p></p><p>5. Fish</p><p></p><p>6. Sepakbola</p><p></p><p>7. There are four yellow banana</p><p></p><p>8. Red and white</p><p></p><p>9. Guru</p><p></p><p>10. Ayah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "a-jawablah-pertanyaan-pertanyaan-berikut-dengan-benar-the-toxt-is-352",
            "question": "A Jawablah pertanyaan-pertanyaan berikut dengan benar    The toxt is for no 12\r\nSita Look at the giraffes. They have curly eyelashes\r\nDini Yes, they do Tholr eyelashes are adorable\r\nSita And look at the zobras. They have black and\r\nwhite stripes on thelr bodies. Andri Guys, do you know\r\nthat each zebra has different pattern?\r\nSita They do? That's very interesting\r\n1. What do they say about the animals?\r\nA. Sila says that giraffes have curly eyelashes\r\nB. Andri says that each zebra has the same patter\r\nC. Sita says that giraffes have black and white stripes\r\nD. Dini says that zebras have curly eyelashes\r\n2 \"Their eyelashes are adorable\" What is the synonym of\r\nthe underlined word?\r\nA. Ugly\r\nC. Awlul\r\nB. Beautiful\r\nD. Bad\r\nThe text is for no 3-6\r\nTHIS IS MY HOUSE\r\na\r\nh\r\nV\r\nIc\r\n7\r\nHello I My name is a Andri and this is my house. My\r\nhouse is a quite big. It has got two floors; a ground floor\r\nand a first floor. It has also got an attic and a basement On\r\nthe ground floor there is the hall, the kitchen, a pantry, the\r\nliving room, a blg dining room and a tollet. On the first floor\r\nthere are three bedrooms, one bathroom and a big\r\ncomidor. My bedroom is between my parents' bedroom and\r\nthe bathroom. My sister's bedroom is in front of mine.\r\nI love my bedroom, but I also like the attic. In the attic\r\n1 keep some of my books and my old toys. I like to spend\r\nmy time there because it is very\r\nspacious and there is a big sofa there where I sometimes take\r\na nap comportable and cozy\r\n9.\r\n3. How many floors are there?\r\nA. There are two floors\r\nB. There is one floor\r\nC. There are two ground floor\r\nD. There are three floors\r\n10.\r\nC\r\n11.\r\n4. Where is the living room?\r\nh. On the first floor\r\nB. On the basement\r\nC. On the ground floor\r\nD. On the second floor\r\nWhy does he like to be in the attic?\r\nA. Because it is very spacious and there is a big sofa thoro\r\nwhere he sometimos take a nap,\r\nB. Because there are two swings and he somoumos play\r\nthere\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>3. a. there are two floor</p><p>4. a. on ghe first floor</p><p>5. a. because it is very spacious and there is a big sofa there where i sometimes tak a nap comportable and cozy</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "d-luna-what-do-you-think-of-the-scenery-here-maya-its-975",
            "question": "D. Luna : What do you think of the scenery here?    Maya : It's ........\r\n................ scenery I have ever seen.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p>it&#039;s <u>the </u><u>best</u> scenery i have ever seen.</p><p></p><p>cmiiw</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "i-am-can-fly-639",
            "question": "I am........ can fly\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bird</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>.................. </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Mine Craft  creative mode</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-month-is-april-an-june-isi-titik2-n-351",
            "question": "The............ month is............. april an june. isi titik2 nya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>the May month is between april and june</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "23-man-how-does-it-feel-if-i-press-here-woman-oh-that-228",
            "question": "23. Man : \"How does it feel if I press here?\u201d    Woman : \"Oh, that hurts.\"\r\nMan : \"I see. You have an appendix. We'll\r\nhave an operation immediately.\"\r\nWhich part of her body hurts?\r\n\r\nA. Nose\r\nB. Ear\r\nC. Eye\r\nD. Throat\r\nE. Stomach\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>E. Stomach</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Appendix = Usus Buntu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>E. Stomach</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>because the womenhave an operation immediately. stomach part</p><p></p><p>may be useful</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-the-girls-are-watching-movie-in-the-cinema-547",
            "question": "2. (+)The girls are watching movie in the\r\ncinema.\r\n(-)..\r\n(?)...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(-) The girls aren&#039;t watching movie in the cinema</p><p>(?) Are The girls watching movie in the\n</p><p>cinema?</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kakkk-bantuuu-dongg-kakk-ltplease-change-into-passive-sent-742",
            "question": "Kakkk bantuuu dongg kakk:\")))    &lt;Please change into passive sentences!&gt;\r\n1.Everbody always expects prosperous life\u200b\r\nkakkk bantu yaa 1 aja",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>prosperous life is always expected by everybody</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}